totalsportek.com 2016-10-31

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and share data and information collected when you visit totalSPORTEK.com. By visiting the site and using the services you agree to terms of this privacy policy. We can be reached via [Contact Us](http://www.totalsportek.com/contact-us/) in case you have any questions regarding the privacy policy, terms and conditions.

#### COOKIES

We might set access cookies which might be stored on your computer upon your first visit to totalSPORTEK.com. “Cookie” is a small file which contains small text, used by majority of the websites, sent and store on your computer’ hard driver in order to uniquely identify the browser you are using, whereas most of the current generation browsers are usually setup to accept cookies by default. You can change the cookies preferences through your browser settings.

#### THIRD PART COOKIES

At totalSPORTEK.com we use third party vendors, for example google, which use cookies to serve advertisement which might be based on your previous visit to the site.

You can read more about how google uses cookies and how you can opt-out by visiting [google advertising terms](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

#### ANALYTICS TOOLS

At totalSPORTEK.com we use google analytics to collect data and information of how visitors use totalsportek.com by collecting only non-personal information which include information like what url you came to totalsportek, IP Address, type of computer and browser, time spent on the site, number of pages accessed at totalSPORTEK and what url you exited from etc.

You can use Google Analytics Opt-out [Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) to prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics. You can read more about this on google analytic out-out page.

#### EXTERNAL LINKS:

Totalsportek.com might contail links to external sites. We are not in any way responsible for privacy and terms of such websites. So you have to review their privacy terms and conditions yourself.

You can always reach out to us if you have any questions about how the data collected through the use of cookies is used and stored at totalSPORTEK.com or if you want to know more about our privacy polices. Use the [Contact Us](http://www.totalsportek.com/contact-us/) page for any questions.
